const STORE = [
    {
        questionNum: 1,
        question: 'Which neighborhood in NYC does Jerry live?',
        option1: 'Upper East Side',
        option2: "Hell's Kitchen",
        option3: 'Upper West Side',
        option4: 'Midtown',
        correctAnswer: 'Upper East Side'
    },
    {
        questionNum: 2,
        question: 'What type of salad does Elaine order when George is paying for lunch? ',
        option1: 'Caesar Salad',
        option2: 'Greek Salad',
        option3: 'Big Salad',
        option4: 'Fruit Salad',
        correctAnswer: 'Big Salad'
    },
    {
        questionNum: 3,
        question: ' Which real life actress does George fall in love with?',
        option1: 'Terri Hatcher',
        option2: 'Marisa Tomei',
        option3: 'Courtney Cox',
        option4: 'Uma Thurman',
        correctAnswer: 'Marisa Tomei'
    },
    {
        questionNum: 4,
        question: 'Where is Elaine originally from? ',
        option1: 'Maryland',
        option2: 'New York',
        option3: 'Maine',
        option4: 'Ohio',
        correctAnswer: 'Maryland'
    },
    {
        questionNum: 5,
        question: 'Which religion does George attempt to convert to? ',
        option1: 'Judaism',
        option2: 'Christianity',
        option3: 'Russian Orthodox',
        option4: 'Latvian Orthodox',
        correctAnswer: 'Latvian Orthodox'
    },
    {
        questionNum: 6,
        question: "What is Kramer's name in the pilot episode?",
        option1: 'Kramer',
        option2: 'Kosmo',
        option3: 'Kessler',
        option4: 'Kensington',
        correctAnswer: 'Kessler'
    },
    {
        questionNum: 7,
        question: "Who is Jerry's arch nemesis? ",
        option1: 'Banya',
        option2: 'Newman',
        option3: 'Soup Nazi',
        option4: 'Mike Moffit',
        correctAnswer: 'Newman'
    },
    {
        questionNum: 8,
        question: "What are George's parents names?",
        option1: 'Fred and Ethel',
        option2: 'Fred and Estelle',
        option3: 'Frank and Ethel',
        option4: 'Frank and Estelle',
        correctAnswer: 'Frank and Estelle'
    },
    {
        questionNum: 9,
        question: 'When Kramer gets the wrong license plate, what does it say? ',
        option1: 'Fusilli',
        option2: 'Assman',
        option3: 'Kramer',
        option4: 'I luv NY',
        correctAnswer: 'Assman'
    },
    {
        questionNum: 10,
        question: "Who is the first to drop out of 'The Contest'?",
        option1: 'Jerry',
        option2: 'George',
        option3: 'Kramer',
        option4: 'Elaine',
        correctAnswer: 'Kramer'
    }
    
]